Excuse me. I'm with Bamboo Productions.
Have you considered a career in entertainment?
Or are you signed with a talent agency—
Oh, Hinata!
Bell?
Let's go!
Huh? Wait a minute!
What was up with that lady?
She wanted to know if I'm interested in
being a model or a performer.
I get asked that sometimes.
Hello there! Welcome!
Oh, Sunohara!
And don't you look lovely today, Bell!
Oh please. Flattery won't
get me to buy anything.
Perceptive one, isn't she?
Seems like Bell's gotten used to
the way things work in this world.
G'morning, Sunohara! G'morning, Bell!
What's the matter?
Something feels off today...
It seems like everyone's staring at Bell...
I might know why.
A Real Dark Elf?
Mysterious Cosplay Babe Sighted!!
Is that me...?!
Is that Bell...?!
Articles like this one get posted
everywhere after SunComi.
Are those love letters?!
It's because I don't have one of those
"smartphones" or whatever.
You hardly see those nowadays...
Guess it just goes to show how serious—
Wh-What are you doing?!
This crap is annoying.
Hinata's the only person I care about.
But don't you feel a little bad for them?
That's not my problem.
I'm not interested in anyone
except you, Hinata.
The day I look another man's way
is the day Hell freezes over.
To me, there are two types of men
in the world: Hinata and other.
Sh-She's obsessed...
C'mon, Hinata.
You and I might as well
flaunt our relationship at school, right?
That way, all these annoying little pests
won't try to get near either of us.
Plus, it'll bring us closer.
Two birds, one stone!
Isn't that right?
Ahem.
Homeroom's about to start!
See ya there!
Wait—!
Jeez, Hinata!
Ah, this sucks...
My shoulders feel like they're falling off...
Bell?!
What's wrong, Sakura?
Where's your bra?!
I'm not wearing one. Too stuffy.
You have to!
Seriously?
C'mere, I'll shield you!
That's all for today.
Gym helpers, collect the soccer balls.
Yes, sir!
Bell...?
Hi-na-ta!
Whoa, Bell—!
I ran a whole bunch, and now I'm tired.
Let's take a breather!
We can't! I have to get back to class—
Really? You're still using that excuse?
You ran away from me this morning, but...
...now you're trapped and can't escape!
Y-You're sweaty.
I-Is that a problem?
I don't... smell bad, do I?
No, that's not...
You always smell nice, Bell.
I do?
Yeah.
M-My bad!
I-I'm sorry! I just...
Don't apologize.
All of me belongs to you, Hinata.
Come on...
No, we shouldn't be doing this!
Aw...
I need to go get changed!
I'll see you later!
Oh, no you don't!
Bell? Are you finished putting away the—
Sakura?!
Mochida?!
Sorry! I'll untie you right now!
Here, open wide.
Consider it an apology.
It's tasty!
Isn't it? Hinata made my lunch himself.
Alright, Hinata, it's my turn.
Go ahead. Feed me.
B-Bell! People are staring at us...
Oh please. Quit using that lame excuse
to try and run away from me.
I'm not "running away," I'm just...
Hey, sorry to interrupt!
So, Bell, about what we discussed
the other day...
Oh, y'mean helping out with club activities?
Yeah. My senpai's here too,
so can we at least have a chat?
Go ahead and eat without me.
I'll be right back.
O-Okay!
Sorry for dragging you away.
Bell's changed a little bit, hasn't she?
What?
Before, she had her walls up
and wouldn't let anyone get near her
except for you, Sunohara.
But lately, she's been pretty friendly
and approachable.
Well... with the other girls, anyway.
For the most part, it seems like
she's adjusted to life in our world.
Yeah, you're right...
I think it's really great...
Heading home at last...
I'm exhausted...
Hey, Hinata? For dinner tonight—
E-Excuse me.
Do I know you...?
Can we help you?
U-Um...
I... Ever since I first laid
eyes on you, Mariabell,
I've been in l-love with you...
I-I wrote you several letters,
but you burned them all...
Still, I need you to know how I feel...
Please be my girlfriend!
B-Bell!
Sorry, but...
...I'm in love with Hinata,
so I can't reciprocate your feelings.
Oh... I see...
I understand.
Let's go, Hinata.
R-Right.
U-Um... Thank you for hearing me out!
Don't give up, okay?
That was delicious!
Alright, I'll go ahead and clean up.
The bath should be warming up now.
Gotcha!
Wh-What's gotten into you, Bell?!
Mm, it looked to me
like you were lost in thought.
Let me guess...
You were worried someone might
swoop in and steal me?
Huh?! That's not...
You're fitting in here really well, and...
...you're improving more and more...
I should be happy, but...
for some reason, it makes me anxious...
It's just... maybe I'm being an idiot, but...
I feel like you're drifting
further away or something...
Hinata, don't think like that...
You don't have faith in me, Hinata!
Oh, how sad! I'm incredibly wounded!
No, that's not true at all!
It's not?
Of course not!
Bingo.
In that case...
...you know the best way to
ease my mind, don't you?
I want to feel as though I belong
to you, Hinata. Body and soul.
Yes! It's finally happening!
Hinata and I will be together at last!
I put in a lot of hard work to make him happy,
and now all the pieces are in place!
Hi-na-ta!
W-Was that good?
NO!
It should be hotter! Deep! Unrelenting!
"Unrelenting"?!
That measly little kiss doesn't
make me feel better at all!
S-Sorry!
Ugh, give me your hand!
If you want me to feel better,
you have to touch me like this...
B-Bell...
There's no need to hold back.
I-I...
I-I'm...
You're...?
I'm sorry!
Hey—! Hinata?!
What do you mean, you're sorry?!
I'm sorry, Bell! Right now, I...
Did I do something to upset you?!
Before I can ease your mind, I need to be...
Hinata?
Hinata, come on!
In the right place...
...and with the right words...
I need to be more clear about my feelings...